<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Azure on Vito Chin</title>
    <link>https://vitochin.com/categories/azure/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Azure on Vito Chin</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://vitochin.com/categories/azure/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Creating a multi-device map with Azure IoT Central</title>
      <link>https://vitochin.com/blog/iotcentralmultidevices/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vitochin.com/blog/iotcentralmultidevices/</guid>
      <description>If you use IoT Central, one of the most common dashboard that you may want to have is a map that shows where your IoT devices are.
Here are 3 steps steps to get such a dashboard.
 1) Add location as a capability
If your devices has the capability to send its location, this should already be configured on your device template. Otherwise, you can add the following capability:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#BulletPoints for Azure SQL Database</title>
      <link>https://vitochin.com/blog/sqldb/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vitochin.com/blog/sqldb/</guid>
      <description>This is my #BulletPoints for Azure SQL Database.
#BulletPoints are my kind of note-taking. I think it helps while learning a new subject or preparing for a certification exam. It may not make much sense if you read it raw, but is a great aide for recall. It usually contains only unique new learnings. You can also use it to check for important points post reading the suggested documents too.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>To queue or not to queue</title>
      <link>https://vitochin.com/blog/queue/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vitochin.com/blog/queue/</guid>
      <description>It’s kind of a tacit art more than science.
It also depends on the motivations of the architect and the team.
Ceteris paribus (i.e. we do not consider application design here), I’ll say there’s the ideal, and there’s the pragmatic.
Ideally, the queue-based load leveling pattern calls for a high throughput queue to be placed before services (such as that for data persistency) as it may be slower (memory vs disk, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>