<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog on Vito Chin</title>
    <link>https://vitochin.com/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blog on Vito Chin</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://vitochin.com/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Pair Blogging: The Epoch</title>
      <link>https://vitochin.com/blog/pairblogging/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vitochin.com/blog/pairblogging/</guid>
      <description>AD:
So how do we write a blog post together Vito?
VC: What do you want to write about?
AD: I don’t know
What should we?
Tech?
Culture?
Life?
Let’s do it bro
VC:
Sure
UX maybe 😊 inclusive UX?
AD:
That isn’t bad
Something we have strong opinions about
Or maybe contrasting opinions
Hah!
VC:
but I tend to eventually agree with yours though 😊
AD:
Other way round lol!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How many transactions does it take to delete 1000 entities in Azure Table Storage?</title>
      <link>https://vitochin.com/blog/table-storage/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vitochin.com/blog/table-storage/</guid>
      <description>Any type of operation against the storage is counted as a transaction, including reads, writes, and deletes.
It takes 2000 transactions to delete 1000 entities.
Explore in Azure Monitoring You can observe this in Azure Monitor, try deleting a
How much does it cost? With entity groups Trivia: You can icnclude up to 100 entities in an entity group transaction.
Caveat This is as per 17th june 2020</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#BulletPoints for Azure SQL Database</title>
      <link>https://vitochin.com/blog/sqldb/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vitochin.com/blog/sqldb/</guid>
      <description>This is my #BulletPoints for Azure SQL Database.
#BulletPoints are my kind of note-taking. I think it helps while learning a new subject or preparing for a certification exam. It may not make much sense if you read it raw, but is a great aide for recall. It usually contains only unique new learnings. You can also use it to check for important points post reading the suggested documents too.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>To queue or not to queue</title>
      <link>https://vitochin.com/blog/queue/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vitochin.com/blog/queue/</guid>
      <description>It’s kind of a tacit art more than science.
It also depends on the motivations of the architect and the team.
Ceteris paribus (i.e. we do not consider application design here), I’ll say there’s the ideal, and there’s the pragmatic.
Ideally, the queue-based load leveling pattern calls for a high throughput queue to be placed before services (such as that for data persistency) as it may be slower (memory vs disk, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Writing, 2020</title>
      <link>https://vitochin.com/blog/2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vitochin.com/blog/2020/</guid>
      <description>In the past, I used to write long form blogs, with proper sentences and paragraphs :)
Restarting my site this 2020, I think it may not be effective anymore:
 Slow to write: which means I write less, not a bad thing, but I want to record more, for memory. Slow to read: I don&amp;rsquo;t think most readers have time / patience to read long form by someone like me, I am not Paul Graham, not that he write too long too.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>